Conservative Party of New York State; Records apap060
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
Conservative Party Of New York State Records1962-2004
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
Conservative Party Of New York State
apap060
40.5 cubic ft.
The Conservative Party Of New York State Records contain files kept for the chairmen of the New York State Conservative Party: Kiernen O’Doherty, 1962; J. Daniel Mahoney, 1962-86; and Serphin Maltese, 1986-88. The strength of the records is in its documentation of New York State politics and elections (including the State Legislature and other state offices), the Conservative Party’s political endorsements and candidates (including writer William F. Buckley, Jr., and Sen. James Buckley), and the political goals and ideological positions on contemporary issues.
Administrative History
The Conservative Party of New York State, also commonly referred to as the New York State Conservative Party, was officially founded in 1962. Efforts to form the party were initiated following the Republican loss of New York State in the 1960 Presidential Election. In 1961 disaffected Republicans, led by New York City attorneys Kiernan O'Doherty and J. Daniel Mahoney, formed the organizing committee for the New York State Conservative Political Association, Inc., a membership corporation. This association was established as a base upon which to build the Conservative Party, "a fourth party, to counter the influence of the New York Liberal Party" [Mahoney, J. Daniel, Actions Speak Louder (New York: Arlington House), p. 24]. The Conservative Party's intent was to "exercise leverage upon the major political parties by endorsing and working for candidates from either party whose views paralleled its own, and running its own candidates where acceptable major party candidates were not put forth" [Mahoney, J. Daniel, Actions Speak Louder (New York: Arlington House), p. 23]
State headquarters opened in April 1962 as the Conservative Party, Inc. which performed the operations of the party through 1962. Due to provisions of the New York State Election Law, the party did not become an official political party until election day of that year. Red-tape was bypassed by taking over and renaming the defunct Freedom Party, Inc. Development of the party began with the creation of local party clubs which were viewed as the party's "main political resource" [Mahoney, J. Daniel, Actions Speak Louder (New York: Arlington House), p. 125]. Interim county committees were formed, and by 1963 there was a county chairman for each of New York State's 62 counties. It was not until 1964 that county committees were elected consisting of two to four members from each election district.
The party's Organizing Committee was redesignated in 1962 as the State Committee and a State Executive Committee was created. The State Committee, like the county committees, was not duly elected until 1964. It consisted of three members from each Congressional district meeting one to two times annually. The State Committee acts as a general oversight body for the party. The State Executive Committee, which meets on a regular basis, controls the implementation of policy. Party officers include the State Chairman, State Vice Chairmen, Secretary and Treasurer. In 1971 the position of Executive Director was instituted to handle many of the administrative details that could no longer be performed by the State Chairman alone.
Chairmen
Kiernan O'Doherty--1962
J. Daniel Mahoney--1962-86
Serphin Maltese--1986-[ ]
Michael R. Long--
Vice Chairmen
Charles Rice--1962-69
Kiernan O'Doherty--1969-86
Executive Director
Serphin Maltese--1971-[ ]
Scope and Contents
The records of the Conservative Party of New York State (hereafter referred to as CPNYS) include party news releases, bulletins, some State Committee and State Executive Committee meeting minutes, election material (such as authorizations and designating petitions of party candidates), party legislative programs, publications, and news clippings. Information on CPNYS candidates is scattered between the Subject Files, which consist primarily of reference material, and the official election campaign documents of the Chairman's Subject Files. The most complete campaign information is that for James L. Buckley's U.S. Senatorial Campaign of 1970. Records related to that campaign are located in the Subject Files and Buckley Files.
The strength of this collection is in the documentation of the CPNYS's positions on social, political and economic issues. The most substantive information is in the News Releases File. Unfortunately that series contains no records for 1967, 1982, 1984 and 1985. News releases for these missing years may be found in the Subject File. The Position Papers also provide valuable information about the party's ideological stance on a limited range of topics (twenty-six). The Legislative Programs in the Chairman's Subject Files provide extensive information on the political goals of the party and are complete except for a major gap from 1979 to 1985. Among the printed materials in the Chairman's Subject Files are reprinted articles and mass mailings. These documents provide an indication of the party's position on a variety of issues.
Although the records span the period from 1962 to 1988 the bulk of the records covers the 1970s and are primarily reference in nature.
An additional 6 cubic feet of records were deposited in August 2004, August 2006, October 2006, and November 2006, but are not yet described in this finding aid.
Arrangement of the Collection
The collection is organized as follows:
Acquisition Information
All items in this manuscript group were donated to the University Libraries, M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives, by the Conservative Party of New York State in March 1989. An additional 6 cubic feet of records were deposited in August 2004, August 2006, October 2006, and November 2006, but are not yet described in this finding aid.
Related Materials
Related collections in the M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives can be found at the subject guides for the New York State Modern Political Archive and Public Servants and Politicians.
Access
Access to this record group is unrestricted.
Africana Studies; Women; Public Servants; New York (State)--Politics and government; Queens County (N.Y.)--Politics and government; New York (State)--Elections; Minutes (administrative records); Photographs; Correspondence; Clippings; Files by subject; O'Doherty, Kiernan; Mahoney, J. Daniel, 1931-; Buckley, William F. (William Frank), d 1925-; Buckley, James; Maltese, Serphin; Rockefeller, Nelson A. (Nelson Aldrich), 1908-1979; Javits, Jacob K. (Jacob Koppel), 1904-1986; Conservative Party of New York State; New York State Conservative Political Association; Liberty Party (U.S.); Republican Party (N.Y.)
- Chairman's Correspondence File, 1963-1966; 1972-1974; 1; 0.5 cubic ft.
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains both incoming and outgoing correspondence of J. Daniel Mahoney, Chairman of the Conservative Party of New York State.
  Arrangement
  Arranged chronologically.
  - Correspondence, 1963-1964 (Box 1 (1-Chairman's Correspondence File), Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1965-1966 (Box 1 (1-Chairman's Correspondence File), Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1972 January-1972 April (Box 1 (1-Chairman's Correspondence File), Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1972 April-1972 September (Box 1 (1-Chairman's Correspondence File), Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1972 September-1972 December (Box 1 (1-Chairman's Correspondence File), Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, Correspondence, 1972 December-1973 February (Box 1 (1-Chairman's Correspondence File), Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1973 February-1973 April (Box 1 (1-Chairman's Correspondence File), Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1973 May-1973 December (Box 1 (1-Chairman's Correspondence File), Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 1974 January-1974 May (Box 1 (1-Chairman's Correspondence File), Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, 1974 January-1974 December (Box 1 (1-Chairman's Correspondence File), Folder 10)
- Chairman's Subject Files, 1962-1988; 2; 6.5 cubic ft.
  This series contains the working files of the Conservative Party Chairman. It includes candidates' authorizations and designating petitions of Conservative Party candidates, election results canvasses, State Committee meeting and State Executive Committee meeting minutes, bulletins, legislative programs, legislative memoranda, committee lists and membership lists, reports, documentation relating to legal cases, party fund raising appeals, and some correspondence. Also included are CPNYS petition instructions which contain a political calendar and list of county chairmen for each year (1968/69, 1971-74, 1976-78). The files include documents created or received by the Executive Director of the CPNYS as well as the party's State Chairman.
  Arranged alphabetically and chronologically.
  - Acceptances of Candidates -- Designation for Public Office, 1965-1986 (Box 1 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Acceptance and Withdrawal of Candidates -- Designation for Public Office, 1977 (Box 1 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Annual Dinner -- 3rd, 1965 (Box 1 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Annual Dinner -- 10th -- Salute to Earl W. Brydges, 1972 (Box 1 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Annual Dinner -- 11th -- Salute to POWs, MIAs, KIAs, 1973 (Box 1 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Annual Dinner -- 12th, 1974 (Box 1 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Annual Dinner -- 13th, 1975 (Box 1 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Annual Dinner -- 14th -- Salute to Senator James Buckley, 1976 (Box 1 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Annual Dinner -- 15th, 1977 (Box 1 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Annual Dinner -- 16th, 1978 (Box 1 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Annual Dinner -- 17th, 1979 (Box 1 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Annual Dinner -- 18th -- Leadership for the '80s, 1980 (Box 1 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Annual Dinners -- Speeches & Dais Lists, 1964-1971 (Box 1 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Annual Dinners, 1974-1976 (Box 1 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Assemblymen with Conservative Party Endorsement, 1975-1976 (Box 1 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Authorizations, Nominations, Acceptances of Candidates, 1972 (Box 1 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Authorizations, Nominations, Acceptances of Candidates, 1973 (Box 1 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Authorizations of Candidates, 1966-1969 (Box 1 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Authorizations of Candidates -- Problems, 1968 (Box 1 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Authorizations of Candidates, 1969 (Box 1 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Authorizations of Candidates, 1970 (Box 1 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Authorizations of Candidates, 1974; 2 folders (Box 1 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 22-23)
  - Authorizations of Candidates, 1976 (Box 1 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - Authorizations of Candidates -- Assembly, 1976 (Box 1 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - Authorizations of Candidates -- Upstate Counties, 1977 (Box 1 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - Authorizations of Candidates, 1978; 4 folders (Box 1 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 27-30)
  - Authorizations of Candidates -- Judiciary, 1978 (Box 1 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 31)
  - Authorizations of Candidates, 1979 (Box 1 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 32)
  - Authorizations of Candidates, 1979 (Box 1 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 33)
  - Authorizations of Candidates -- Otsego County, 1979 (Box 1 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 34)
  - Authorizations of Candidates -- Senate, 1979 (Box 2 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Authorizations of Candidates, 1980 (Box 2 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Authorizations of Candidates -- Problems, 1980 (Box 2 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Authorizations of Candidates, 1981 (Box 2 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Authorizations of Candidates, 1982 (Box 2 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Authorizations of Candidates, 1982 (Box 2 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Authorizations of Candidates, 1984 (Box 2 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Authorizations of Candidates, 1986 (Box 2 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Authorizations of Candidates, Requests, 1978 (Box 2 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Authorizations of Candidates, Requests, 1980 (Box 2 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Authorizations of Candidates, Requests, 1985 (Box 2 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Authorizations of Candidates, Requests, 1987 (Box 2 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Bulletins, 1962 (Box 2 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Bulletins, ca. 1963 (Box 2 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Bulletins, 1967 (Box 2 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Bulletins, 1971 (Box 2 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Bulletins, 1974 (Box 2 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Bulletins, 1975 (Box 2 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Bulletins, 1976 January-1976 April (Box 2 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Bulletins, 1976 April-1976 December (Box 2 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Bulletins, 1977 (Box 2 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Bulletins, 1978 (Box 2 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - Bulletins, 1979 (Box 2 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - Bulletins, 1980 (Box 2 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - Bulletins, 1981 (Box 2 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - Bulletins, 1985 (Box 2 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - Bulletins, 1986 (Box 2 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - Candidates, 1964 (Box 2 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 28)
    Contains lists of Conservative Party candidates.
  - Candidates, 1965 (Box 2 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - Candidates, 1966 (Box 2 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - Candidates, 1968 (Box 2 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 31)
  - Candidates, 1969 (Box 2 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 32)
  - Candidates, 1970 (Box 2 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 33)
  - Candidates, 1971 (Box 2 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 34)
  - Candidates, 1972 (Box 2 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 35)
  - Candidates, 1973 (Box 2 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 36)
  - Candidates -- N.Y. County, 1981-1982 (Box 2 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 37)
  - Congress -- Members Endorsed by Conservative Party, 1974 (Box 2 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 38)
  - Congressmen -- With Conservative Endorsement, Elected, 1974 November (Box 2 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 39)
  - Conservative County Committee, 1980 (Box 2 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 40)
  - County, Albany, 1976 (Box 2 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 41)
    County files contain clippings, correspondence and other material on Conservative Party county committees and candidates.
  - County, Allegheny, 1977 (Box 2 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 42)
  - County, Broome, 1976-1977; 1980 (Box 2 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 43)
  - County, Bronx, 1977 (Box 2 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 44)
  - County, Cattaraugus, 1966 (Box 2 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 45)
  - County, Cayuga, 1965; 1978; 1984; 1986 (Box 2 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 46)
  - County, Chautauqua, 1978 (Box 2 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 47)
  - County, Clinton, 1977 (Box 2 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 48)
  - County, Cortland, 1977 (Box 2 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 49)
  - County, Delaware, 1978; 1986 (Box 2 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 50)
  - County, Dutchess, 1978 (Box 2 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 51)
  - County, Erie, 1978; 1984 (Box 2 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 52)
  - County, Franklin, 1977; 1985 (Box 2 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 53)
  - County, Fulton, 1977 (Box 2 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 54)
  - County, Herkimer, 1985 (Box 2 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 55)
  - County, Jefferson, 1977 (Box 2 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 56)
  - County, Kings, 1977 (Box 2 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 57)
  - County, Lewis, 1977 (Box 2 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 58)
  - County, Madison, 1977 (Box 2 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 59)
  - County, Monroe, 1984 (Box 2 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 60)
  - County, Nassau, 1974; 1976; 1980-1981; 1983 (Box 2 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 61)
  - County, Oneida, 1977; 1982 (Box 2 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 62)
  - County, Onondaga, 1977-1978; 1980-1983; 1986 (Box 2 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 63)
  - County, Ontario, 1974; 1978 (Box 2 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 64)
  - County, Otsego, 1985 (Box 2 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 65)
  - County, Oswego, 1977; 1982 (Box 2 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 66)
  - County, Putnam, 1979 (Box 2 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 67)
  - County, Queens, 1977-1979 (Box 2 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 68)
  - County, Rensselaer, 1977 (Box 2 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 69)
  - County, Richmond, 1976 (Box 2 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 70)
  - County, Rockland, 1978 (Box 2 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 71)
  - County, St. Lawrence, 1977 (Box 2 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 72)
  - County, Saratoga, 1976 (Box 2 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 73)
  - County, Schenectady, 1978 (Box 2 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 74)
  - County, Schoharie, 1977; 1985-1986 (Box 2 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 75)
  - County, Schuyler, 1974; 1977 (Box 2 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 76)
  - County, Seneca, 1977 (Box 2 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 77)
  - County, Suffolk, 1978; 1980; 1984 (Box 2 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 78)
  - County, Sullivan, 1977; 1983-1984 (Box 2 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 79)
  - County, Warren, 1969 (Box 2 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 80)
  - County, Washington, 1977 (Box 2 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 81)
  - County, Wayne, 1977 (Box 2 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 82)
  - County, Westchester, 1983-1984 (Box 2 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 83)
  - County, Wyoming, 1978 (Box 2 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 84)
  - County, Yates, 1975 (Box 2 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 85)
  - County Committees, Organization of, 1968-1969 (Box 2 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 86)
  - County Officers Count, 1966; 1970; 1974-1980 (Box 2 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 87)
  - Declination of Candidates of Nomination to Public Office, 1974; 1982 (Box 2 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 88)
  - Designation, Certificates of, 1974 (Box 2 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 89)
  - Designation, Certificate of, 1976 (Box 2 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 90)
  - Designation, Certificate of, 1986 (Box 2 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 91)
  - Dinner -- Victory Dinner to Honor Senator James L. Buckley, 1971 (Box 2 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 92)
  - Dinners -- General, 1963; 1968-1971 (Box 2 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 93)
  - Dinner Journals, 1967-1968 (Box 2 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 94)
    Includes financial information.
  - Election Analysis -- Nassau County, 1978 (Box 3 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Election Calendar, 1979 (Box 3 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Election -- Judges, Undated (Box 3 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Election -- Queens County Candidates, 1973 (Box 3 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Election -- Special, 1973 (Box 3 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Election Results, 1962 (Box 3 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Election Results, 1969 (Box 3 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Election Results -- NYC Mayor, 1969 (Box 3 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Election Results, 1970 (Box 3 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Election Results, 1971 (Box 3 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Election Results, 1972 (Box 3 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Election Results, 1973 (Box 3 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Election Results -- Primary, 1973 (Box 3 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Election Results -- Governor (by Assembly District), 1974; 2 folders (Box 3 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 14-15)
  - Election Results -- Governor (Queens County), 1974 (Box 3 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Election Results, 1974 (Box 3 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Election Results, 1975 (Box 3 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Election Results, 1976 (Box 3 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Election Results -- New York State, 1977 (Box 3 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Election Results, 1978 (Box 3 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Election Results -- By Assembly & Senate Districts, 1978 (Box 3 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - Election Results -- By Counties, 1978; 2 folders (Box 3 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 23-24)
  - Election Results -- New York State, 1978 (Box 3 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - Election Results -- Primary, 1978 (Box 3 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - Election Results, 1979 (Box 3 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - Election Results, By County, 1979 (Box 3 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - Election Results, Judge of the Civil Court, 4th Municipal District, 1979 (Box 3 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - Election Results -- Queens County, 1979 (Box 3 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - Election Results -- Yates County, 1979 (Box 3 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 31)
  - Election Results, 1980 (Box 3 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 32)
  - Election Results -- By Assembly District, ca. 1980 (Box 3 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 33)
  - Election Results -- Primary, 1980 (Box 3 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 34)
  - Elections -- Marginal Districts, 1962; 1964; 1970 (Box 3 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 35)
  - Elections -- Poll Watchers, 1962-1963 (Box 3 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 36)
  - Elections -- Local Races, 1964 (Box 3 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 37)
  - Elections -- Qualification of Minor & New Parties for Place on the Ballot, 1964 (Box 3 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 38)
  - Elections -- General, 1965 (Box 3 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 39)
  - Elections -- New York City, 1965 (Box 3 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 40)
  - Elections -- Registration, 1965 (Box 3 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 41)
  - Elections -- 17th Congressional District, 1965 (Box 3 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 42)
  - Elections -- State, 1965 (Box 3 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 43)
  - Elections -- Voting Machines, 1964-1965 (Box 3 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 44)
  - Elections -- Congressional, 1966 (Box 3 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 45)
  - Elections -- Upstate, 1966 (Box 3 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 46)
  - Elections, 1967 (Box 3 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 47)
  - Elections -- Judicial, 1973 (Box 3 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 48)
  - Elections -- Queens County, 1974 (Box 3 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 49)
  - Elections -- Canvass of Votes, Suffolk County, 1977 (Box 3 (2-Chairman's Subject Files), Folder 50)